A Guide to the John C. Watkins Papers 1979-1999
Virginia Commonwealth University, James Branch Cabell Library
- Series II-Office Files 1984-1997
  - Senate Tax Bills 1992 (Box 61)
  - Senate Finance Dockets 1996 (Box 61)
  - September Correspondence 1992-1996 (Box 61)
  - Sewage 1994 (Box 61)
  - Short Term Rental (HB 1410) (Box 61)
  - Shrink Swell Soil 1993 (Box 61)
  - Solid Waste Management (HB 1540) 1987 (Box 61)
  - Spec. Highway Construction Fund (HB 657) 1988 (Box 61)
  - Speeches 1992 (Box 61)
  - Speed Detectors 1993 (Box 61)
  - Speed Limits 1987-1994 (Box 61)
  - Sprinklers (HB 656) 1988 (Box 61)
  - State Board of Elections 1992 (Box 62)
  - State Corporation Commission 1993 (Box 62)
  - State Correspondence 1996 (Box 62)
  - State of Commonwealth Address 1996 (Box 62)
  - State Employees 1991-1993 (Box 62)
  - State and Local Bonds Tax Immunity (HJR 53) 1990 (Box 62)
  - State Police 1992-1994 (Box 62)
  - State Recordation Taxes 1993 (Box 62)
  - State Song 1992-1997 (Box 62)
  - Statue of Limitations (HB 537) 1984 (Box 62)
  - St. Mary's 1992 (Box 62)
  - Stream Rights 1992 (Box 62)
  - Streptocauccus Resolution (SJR 51) 1996 (Box 62)
  - Student Letters 1993 (Box 62)
  - Subdivision Ordinances (HB 658) 1988 (Box 62)
  - Sunshine Coalition 1997 (Box 62)
  - Surveys 1993 (Box 62)
  - Tax Cuts 1994 (Box 62)
  - Tax Exempt/Girl Scouts 1989 (Box 62)
  - Tax Form/Voter Registration (HB 282) 1994 (Box 62)
  - Tax Increases 1992 (Box 62)
  - Tax 911 1994 (Box 62)
  - Tax Policy Commission 1997 (Box 62)
  - Tax Withholding Allowance (HB 1475) 1996 (Box 62)
  - Tech Budget Amendments 1997 (Box 62)
  - Telecommunications 1996-1997 (Box 62)
  - Telephone Bill 1993 (Box 62)
  - Telephone Charges Disclosures 1990 (Box 62)
  - Tent Sales 1997 (Box 62)
  - Term Limits 1992 (Box 62)
  - Term List 1995-1996 (Box 62)
  - Terry Stop/Frisk (HB 796) 1994 (Box 62)
  - Textbooks 1993 (Box 62)
  - Thanks/Congrats 1994 (Box 62)
  - Title Insurance/Bankers 1993 (Box 62)
  - Title Insurance (HB 613) 1996 (Box 62)
  - Tobacco 1992 (Box 62)
  - Toll Road Authority (HB 1572) 1997 (Box 62)
  - Tom's Creek 1992-1993 (Box 62)
  - Tracking Bills 1994 (Box 62)
  - Trademark Bills 1997 (Box 62)
  - Transient Occupancy Tax (HB 1470) 1996 (Box 62)
  - Transportation 1993 (Box 62)
  - Transportation Bonds 1992 (Box 62)
  - Transportation District (HB 412) 1986 (Box 62)
  - Trees/Facts 1990 (Box 62)
  - Trespass 1987 (Box 62)
  - Trigon 1995 (Box 62)
  - Trigon Conversion 1996 (Box 62)
  - Typed Responses 1994 (Box 62)
  - Tuition Assistance Grant 1994 (Box 62)
  - Tyler Community College/Midlothian 1995 (Box 62)
  - United Network for Organ Sharing (HB 1182) 1991 (Box 63)
  - Urban Highways (HB 777) 1992 (Box 63)
  - Urban Partnership 1996 (Box 63)
  - USDA/Reorganization Plan 1995 (Box 63)
  - U.S. Supreme Court-First Eng. Lutheran vs. LA County 1989 (Box 63)
  - Use and Loose Juvenile Alcohol 1995 (Box 63)
  - Utility Taxes (HB 663) 1986 (Box 63)
  - U.R. (HB 1973) 1995 (Box 63)
  - Utilization Review 1995-1997 (Box 63)
  - Variance Clarification (HB 644) 1984 (Box 63)
  - Variation Zoning (HB 444) 1984 (Box 63)
  - Vascar (HB 609) 1996 (Box 63)
  - VCU 1992-1994 (Box 63)
  - Vegetative Waste 1996 (Box 63)
  - Vehicles (HB 1643) 1985 (Box 63)
  - Vehicular Homicide (HB 772) 1992 (Box 63)
  - Venue/Civil Cases (HB 1079) 1990 (Box 63)
  - Veterinarians 1993 (Box 63)
  - VGIA Considerations 1996 (Box 63)
  - VGIN 1995-1996 (Box 63)
  - Viatical Settlements 1997 (Box 63)
  - Video Prohibitions (HB 1057) 1988 (Box 63)
  - Video/Rating (HB 660) 1988 (Box 63)
  - Violence Resolution (HJR 182) 1988 (Box 63)
  - VA Beach/Lake Gaston 1995 (Box 63)
  - Va Corn Board (HB 1375) 1987 (Box 63)
  - VA Department of Youth and Family Services-Max. Security Fac. 1994 (Box 63)
  - VA Dietetic Association 1995 (Box 64)
  - VA Fertilizer Act 1995 (Box 64)
  - VA Geographic Information Authority 1996 (Box 64)
  - VA Institute of Government Advisory-Board Meeting 1995 (Box 64)
  - VA Outdoors Foundation 1990 (Box 64)
  - VA Perinatal Association 1993 (Box 64)
  - VA Pesticide Act 1995 (Box 64)
  - VA Power 1996 (Box 64)
  - VA Public Building Authority 1992 (Box 64)
  - VA Tech Extension 1995-1996 (Box 64)
  - VA Tech 1992-194 (Box 64)
  - Virginia Health Care Foundation 1993 (Box 64)
  - Virginia Port Authority 1990 (Box 64)
  - Virginia Power 1993-1994 (Box 64)
  - Virginia Supreme Court Vacancy 1997 (Box 64)
  - Virginia Retirement System 1996 (Box 64)
  - VMI 1992-1994 (Box 64)
  - Vocal-Virginia 1989 (Box 64)
  - Vote on Tax Raises 1994 (Box 64)
  - Voters Lists 1994-1995 (Box 64)
  - Voter Registration 1997 (Box 64)
  - Voting Machines 1990 (Box 64)
  - Voting Rights Act 1983-1994 (Box 64)
  - VPI and SU Budget Amendment 1987 (Box 64)
  - VRS investments (HB 644) 1992 (Box 64)
  - VTAG Correspondence 1996 (Box 64)
  - Waste Management 1992 (Box 64)
  - Waste Tire Trust 1993 (Box 64)
  - Waste Tire 1996 (Box 64)
  - Water Control Board 1992 (Box 64)
  - Water Quality Budget Amendment 1997 (Box 64)
  - Watkins Resume 1993 (Box 64)
  - Watson 1996 (Box 64)
  - Weed, Trash Removal 1983 (Box 64)
  - Weighing Vehicles (HB 261) 1986 (Box 64)
  - Wet Settlement 1996 (Box 64)
  - Wilder 1992 (Box 64)
  - Wilder Speech 1995 (Box 64)
  - Wildlife-Consolidation 1996 (Box 64)
  - Windshields 1988 (Box 64)
  - Wine ABC (HB 493) 1983 (Box 64)
  - Wine Franchise 1996 (Box 64)
  - Wolf Dogs 1992-1997 (Box 64)
  - Wolf Hybrids 1996 (Box 64)
  - Woodlake 1991 (Box 64)
  - Workers Compensation 1987 (Box 64)
  - Workers Compensation Insurance 1992-1993 (Box 64)
  - Workmans Compensation 1987, 1993-1994 (Box 64)
  - Workmans Compensation Merge Enclosures: (HB 2366, 2556, 2559) 1997 (Box 64)
  - Worker Compensation Vacancies 1997 (Box 64)
  - Work Session 1993 (Box 64)
  - WWBT (HJR 65) 1990 (Box 64)
  - Youth Institutional Violence (HB 2192) 1995 (Box 64)
  - Zoning Ordinances-penalties (HB 635) 1990 (Box 64)
- Series III--Office Files, n.d. 1977-1999
  - ABC-Privatization 1997 (Box 65)
  - ABC/Wine 1998-1999 (Box 65)
  - Aborist Registration 1989 (Box 65)
  - Abortion, n.d. 1982-1991 (Box 65)
  - Abortion 1998 (Box 65)
  - Abortion 1999 (Box 65)
  - Acid Rain, n.d. (Box 65)
  - ACLU 1984 (Box 65)
  - Adequate Public Facilities (SB 355) 1999 (Box 65)
  - Adequate Public Facilities Ordinance (HB 355) 1998 (Box 65)
  - Agriculture Alumni, n.d. 1988, 1991-1992 (Box 65)
  - Agriculture/Farmers Market 1987-1988 (Box 65)
  - Agriculture/Tobacco, n.d. 1993-1994 (Box 65)
  - Airport Access Roads (HB 485) 1998 (Box 65)
  - Alcoholic Beverage License (HB 522) 1998 (Box 65)
  - Ambulance Authority-Richmond 1997 (Box 65)
  - Animals 1999 (Box 65)
  - Animal Cruelty (SB 851) 1999 (Box 65)
  - Animal Feeding Operations (HB 661) 1998 (Box 65)
  - Appointments 1998 (Box 65)
  - Appointments 1999 (Box 65)
  - Appointments to Commissions 1999 (Box 65)
  - Augmented Estate, n.d. 1990 (Box 65)
  - Automotive Legislation, n.d. 1998 (Box 65)
  - Bailes 1985-1989 (Box 65)
  - Banking 1988 (Box 65)
  - Banking and /or Credit Unions 1998 (Box 65)
  - Benedetti's Bills 1997-1998 (Box 65)
  - Billboards, n.d. 1997-1998 (Box 65)
  - Billboards Letters 1998 (Box 65)
  - Bills 1999 (Box 65)
  - Bills 1999 (Box 65)
  - Blue Cross Blue Shield, n.d. 1988-1990 (Box 65)
  - BPOL Developer List 1997 (Box 65)
  - BPOL Tax 1995-1996 (Box 65)
  - Bond Issues, n.d. (Box 65)
  - Brandermill Retirement 1983-1984, 1986 (Box 65)
  - Bridge Named for Hardaway Marks (Crater PDC) 1997 (Box 65)
  - Budget 1993 (Box 65)
  - Budget Information 1997 (Box 65)
  - Budget Requests, n.d. 1997 (Box 65)
  - Budget 1998 (Box 65)
  - Budget Education 1999 (Box 65)
  - Building Inspection/Shrink-Swell Soils, n.d. 1989-1992 (Box 65)
  - Building Regulations, n.d. 1992 (Box 65)
  - Bureau of Insurance 1995 (Box 65)
  - Bus Transit 1998 (Box 65)
  - C and P Telephone, n.d. 1977-1984 (Box 65)
  - Campaign/State Board of Elections 1985 (Box 65)
  - Capital Area Assembly, n.d. 1989-1991 (Box 65)
  - Car Tax 1997-1998 (Box 65)
  - Census 1990, n.d. 1988-1993 (Box 65)
  - Center for Innovative Technology 1986-1987 (Box 66)
  - Central Virginia Caucus, n.d. 1996 (Box 66)
  - Central Virginia Caucus 1997 (Box 66)
  - Chesapeake Bay Bridge and Tunnel Commission 1989 (Box 66)
  - Chesapeake Bay Foundation/Environmental Defense Fund Petition 1993 (Box 66)
  - Chesapeake Bay Preservation Act 1991 (Box 66)
  - Chesapeake Bay Regulations, n.d. 1990-1991 (Box 66)
  - Chesterfield/Cash Proffers 1989 (Box 66)
  - Chesterfield Charter, n.d. 1986 (Box 66)
  - Chesterfield County Planning Department Management Study 1996 (Box 66)
  - Chesterfield County Republican Committee, n.d. 1984-1987 (Box 66)
  - Chesterfield/Detention Home 1984 (Box 66)
  - Chesterfield Grants, n.d. 1982-1989 (Box 66)
  - Chesterfield HMK 1982-1983 (Box 66)
  - Chesterfield/Infrastructure 1992 (Box 66)
  - Chesterfield Issues, n.d. 1982-1989 (Box 66)
  - Chesterfield Issues 1990-1993 (Box 66)
  - Chesterfield/Legislative Program 1988, 1990-1991, 1993, 1995 (Box 66)
  - Chesterfield Legislative 1995-1998 (Box 66)
  - Chesterfield/Magnolia Grange 1989, 1992 (Box 66)
  - Chesterfield Schools 1988-1989, 1991-1992, 1995 and 1997 (Box 66)
  - Chesterfield Senatorial Committee 1986 (Box 66)
  - Chesterfield Social Services (Group Homes) 1985-1990 (Box 66)
  - Chesterfield Transportation, n.d. 1993-1995 (Box 66)
  - Chesterfield Waste Treatment 1984-1986 (Box 66)
  - Chesterfield Water, n.d. 1988 (Box 66)
  - Child Support Services-Sandy Banks-Bertwell 1998 (Box 66)
  - Children's Health 1998 (Box 66)
  - Children's Health 1999 (Box 66)
  - Children's Health Insurance (SB 433) 1998 (Box 66)
  - Children's Medical Security Insurance Plan 1998 (Box 66)
  - Chiropractors (HB 2067) 1999 (Box 66)
  - CIB Telecom 1997 (Box 66)
  - Cities-Regional Cooperation 1998 (Box 66)
  - Civil Rights (HB 240) 1998 (Box 66)
  - Clarence Williams for Sheriff, n.d. 1990 (Box 66)
  - Clean Air Act 1989 (Box 66)
  - Clinton Miller 1992-1993 (Box 66)
  - CNR Subcommittee, n.d. 1998 (Box 66)
  - Coal and Energy Commission, n.d. 1995-1997 (Box 66)
  - Colonial Heights 1982 (Box 66)
  - Commercial Driver Licensing 1988-1989 (Box 66)
  - Commercial Vehicles on Lanes of Interstate Highways 1997 (Box 66)
  - Commission on Local Government (Grayson Commission) 1989 (Box 66)
  - Conditional Zoning, n.d. 1986, 1989, 1990, 1994 (Box 67)
  - Conference Committees 1994 (Box 67)
  - Conflict of Interest Act 1983-1987 (Box 67)
  - Congratulations 1998 (Box 67)
  - Congratulations 1999 (Box 67)
  - Conservation Issues/Bills 1988 (Box 67)
  - Constitutional Amendments, n.d. 1990 (Box 67)
  - Constitutional Convention 1977, 1985-1986 (Box 67)
  - Continuous Electron Beam Accelerator Facility (CEBAF), n.d. 1988-1989 (Box 67)
  - Cordle, John/Treasurer 1991 (Box 67)
  - Corrections 1999 (Box 67)
  - Correspondence, n.d. 1990-1992 (Box 67)
  - Correspondence, January 1991 (Box 67)
  - Correspondence, February 1991 (Box 67)
  - Correspondence, March 1991 (Box 67)
  - Correspondence, April 1991 (Box 67)
  - Correspondence, May 1991 (Box 67)
  - Correspondence, June 1991 (Box 67)
  - Correspondence, July 1991 (Box 67)
  - Correspondence, August 1991 (Box 67)
  - Correspondence, September 1991 (Box 67)
  - Correspondence, November 1991 (Box 67)
  - Correspondence, December 1991 (Box 67)
  - Correspondence 1997 (Box 67)
  - Correspondence 1997-1998 (Box 67)
  - Correspondence-Veto Session 1998 (Box 67)
  - County of Powhatan 1991 (Box 67)
  - Courthouse Road 1995 (Box 67)
  - Credit Union 1999 (Box 67)
  - Dameron (Lives at Executive Inn) 1998 (Box 67)
  - Debris Waste Disposal, n.d. 1987-1992 (Box 67)
  - Diabetes 1997 (Box 67)
  - Diabetes/School (SB 889) 1999 (Box 67)
  - Disclosure Committee, n.d. 1989-1990 (Box 67)
  - Disney/Disney's America, n.d. 1993 (Box 67)
  - Disney America 1994 (Box 67)
  - District Dourt, n.d. 1998-1991 (Box 67)
  - Drafting Bills-Instruction 1997 (Box 67)
  - Drivers Licenses 1998 (Box 67)
  - Drug Rehab-Tough Love, n.d. 1983-1987 (Box 67)
  - Drunk Driving/Drinking, n.d. 1982-1987 (Box 67)
  - DuPont Spruance Plant, n.d. 1989 (Box 67)
  - Dykes vs. Nova Transportation 1991 (Box 67)
  - E-mail correspondence 1999 (Box 67)
  - E-mail from Constituents 1998 (Box 67)
  - Eagle Scout 1998 (Box 67)
  - Easement Agreement for Richard Rose 1981 (Box 67)
  - Education 1998 (Box 67)
  - Education 1995-1996 (Box 68)
  - Education Disparity, n.d. 1991-1993 (Box 68)
  - Education Issues 1988-1994 (Box 68)
  - EITC 1998 (Box 68)
  - El Rancho Trailer Court 1994-1995 (Box 68)
  - Election Law Definitions (HB 47) 1999 (Box 68)
  - Electric Utility Deregulation 1998 (Box 68)
  - Electrologist 1997 (Box 68)
  - EMS-$4-For-Life Bill 1997 (Box 68)
  - Emergency Release Orders 1997 (Box 68)
  - Endangered Species, n.d. 1984, 1989, 1991 (Box 68)
  - Endangered Species, n.d. 1992 (Box 68)
  - Engineers Licensure Law 1988 (Box 68)
  - Environment 1998 (Box 68)
  - Environment 1999 (Box 68)
  - Evaluation of Water Quality, n.d. 1996 (Box 68)
  - Fair Business Practice Act (SB 1176) 1999 (Box 68)
  - Family Life Education, n.d. 1986-1989 (Box 68)
  - Family Life Education-Opt Out Program, n.d. 1989 (Box 68)
  - Federal/Corporate Take-over, n.d. 1987 (Box 68)
  - Federal Retirees 1994 (Box 68)
  - Fertility Insurance (HB 2403) 1999 (Box 68)
  - Fertilizer 1999 (Box 68)
  - Finance 1999 (Box 68)
  - Fire Management-Railroads, n.d. 1965-1982 (Box 68)
  - First Annual Report of the U.S.A. 1995 (Box 68)
  - Flags 1997-1998 (Box 68)
  - Food Lion 1993 (Box 68)
  - 4-H Fund, n.d. 1984-1985 (Box 68)
  - Funny File, n.d. 1998 (Box 68)
  - Focus Chesterfield 1991-1993 (Box 68)
  - Gambling 1992 (Box 68)
  - General Assembly Bill Action, n.d. 1987-1988 (Box 68)
  - General Assembly/Ratings 1982-1987, 1994 (Box 68)
  - General Assembly/Survey 1982, 1984-1987, 1989-1992 (Box 68)
  - General Assembly Veto Session 1984-1988 (Box 68)
  - General Assembly Veto Session, n.d. 1990 (Box 68)
  - General Correspondence 1998 (Box 68)
  - General Correspondence, 1 of 2, January 1999 (Box 68)
  - General Correspondence, 2 of 2, January 1999 (Box 68)
  - General Correspondence, 1 of 5, February 1999 (Box 68)
  - General Correspondence, 2 of 5, February 1999 (Box 68)
  - General Correspondence, 3 of 5, February 1999 (Box 68)
  - General Correspondence, 4 of 5, February 1999 (Box 68)
  - General Correspondence, 5 of 5, February 1999 (Box 69)
  - General Obligation Bond Issue, n.d. 1991-1992 (Box 69)
  - General Permit-Complaint 1993, 1995-1998 (Box 69)
  - General Permit 1998 (Box 69)
  - George Allen, n.d. 1993 (Box 69)
  - George Washington-CVN 73 1992 (Box 69)
  - Gilmore vs. Lansidle and Jamerson 1996 (Box 69)
  - Girone, Joan Campaign, n.d. 1986-1987 (Box 69)
  - Golden Rule 1998 (Box 69)
  - Governor Robb 1982-1991 (Box 69)
  - Grange Hall Resolution 1997 (Box 69)
  - Grants/Commission for the Arts, n.d. 1982-1996 (Box 69)
  - Grants/Department of Education 1983-1987 (Box 69)
  - Grants/Department of Historic Resources 1991-1995 (Box 69)
  - Grayson Commission 1988-1989 (Box 69)
  - Grayson Commission 1990 (Box 69)
  - Grayson Commission 1991 (Box 69)
  - Grove Rezoning Case 1997 (Box 69)
  - Gun Control 1989, 1991, 1993 (Box 69)
  - Gun Control 1999 (Box 69)
  - Guns 1998 (Box 69)
  - Hansboro (Dream), n.d. (Box 69)
  - Harper vs. Virginia, n.d. 1993-1995 (Box 69)
  - Hate Crimes 1998 (Box 69)
  - HB 306 1998 (Box 69)
  - HB 335/Powhite 1983-1984 (Box 69)
  - Health 1987-1988 (Box 69)
  - Health Benefits Program-Budget Amendments 1997 (Box 69)
  - Health Care January 1998 (Box 69)
  - Health Care February 1998 (Box 69)
  - Health Care March 1998 (Box 69)
  - Health Care, 1 of 4, December 1998 (Box 69)
  - Health Care, 2 of 4, January 1999 (Box 69)
  - Health Care, 3 of 4, February 1999 (Box 69)
  - Health Care, 4 of 4, February 1999 (Box 69)
  - Helmet Law (HB 1069) 1998 (Box 69)
  - Hemp 1998 (Box 69)
  - Henrico 1997-1998 (Box 69)
  - Henrico Legislative Package 1997-1998 (Box 69)
  - Henricus Foundation 1997 (Box 69)
  - Highway Construction/Special Projects 1976, 1980 (Box 69)
  - Highways 1985-1986 (Box 70)
  - Highways/Bonding 1986-1987 (Box 70)
  - Highways/General, n.d. 1983-1984 (Box 70)
  - Highways/JLARC 1984 (Box 70)
  - Historic Preservation, n.d. 1986, 1989-1990 (Box 70)
  - HMO's 1997-1998 (Box 70)
  - Holiday Card 1998 (Box 70)
  - House Bills, n.d. 1992 (Box 70)
  - House of Delegates, n.d. 1994-1997 (Box 70)
  - House of Delegates/Clerk 1983-1992 (Box 70)
  - House of Delegates Committee Votes 1985-1993 (Box 70)
  - House of Delegates Patron Reports 1985-1990 (Box 70)
  - House of Delegates/Professional Assistance Today 1985-1987 (Box 70)
  - House/Page 1992-1994 (Box 70)
  - HOW Insurance Company 1994 (Box 70)
  - Hunting Blinds 1998 (Box 70)
  - Hunting Licenses 1998 (Box 70)
  - I-295 Location/Design 1982-1987 (Box 70)
  - I-85/95 Connector, n.d. 1983-1984, 1987 (Box 70)
  - I-895 Connector 1988-1989 (Box 70)
  - I-95/85 Connector Impact Statement 1984 (Box 70)
  - Identity Theft 1997 (Box 70)
  - Impact Fees 1987-1988 (Box 70)
  - Impact Fees, n.d. 1989-1991, 1994 (Box 70)
  - Impact Fees, n.d. 1990-1992 (Box 70)
  - Impact Fees 1992, 1998 (Box 70)
  - Impact Fees (SB 48) 1989-1991 (Box 70)
  - Impact Fees Subcommittee, n.d. 1990-1991 (Box 70)
  - Insurance, n.d. 1986-1989 (Box 70)
  - Insurance/98-Medical-Dental 1995, 1997 (Box 70)
  - Inter-basin Transfer of Water 1982 (Box 70)
  - Internet Agreement 1998 (Box 70)
  - Intersections: Courthouse/Providence 1986 (Box 70)
  - Interstate Waste 1998 (Box 70)
  - IPP/SCC Regulation 1989 (Box 70)
  - Issues Related to Harper Legislation 1994 (Box 70)
  - John Tyler Community College, n.d. 1988, 1994 (Box 70)
  - John Tyler Community College 1996 (Box 70)
  - Judges, n.d. 1998-1999 (Box 70)
  - Judges, n.d. 1998-1999 (Box 70)
  - Judges, n.d. 1998-1999 (Box 70)
  - Judgeship Correspondence 1998 (Box 70)
  - Judgeships, n.d. 1998 (Box 70)
  - Judicial Inquiry and Review Commission 1997 (Box 70)
  - Judicial Interviews 1998 (Box 70)
  - Judicial Nominations 1997 (Box 70)
  - Judy Worthington 1991 (Box 70)
  - Keever Virginia Tech 1997 (Box 71)
  - Labor Day School Openings 1997-1998 (Box 71)
  - Landsat, n.d. 1981-1982 (Box 71)
  - Landscape Architecture Licensure, n.d. 1982-1989 (Box 71)
  - Legislative Inquiries, n.d. 1981-1984 (Box 71)
  - Legislative Priorities-Watkins to Gilmore 1998 (Box 71)
  - Legislative Services Issue 1990-1991 (Box 71)
  - Letter from Niall Paul 1989 (Box 71)
  - License Plates Choose Life 1999 (Box 71)
  - License Plates "Confederate" 1999 (Box 71)
  - Literary Fund 1986 (Box 71)
  - Local Government 1999 (Box 71)
  - Lorraine's Correspondence 1998 (Box 71)
  - Lottery, n.d. 1986-1994 (Box 71)
  - Lottery Building, n.d. 1993 (Box 71)
  - Low Emission Vehicles 1998 (Box 71)
  - Lucas vs. South Carolina Coastal Council 1992 (Box 71)
  - Mechanics Lien Study 1992 (Box 71)
  - Maglev Project at Virginia Tech-Electric Cars 1998 (Box 71)
  - Maglev Technology-High Speed Transportation 1997 (Box 71)
  - Managed Care 1999 (Box 71)
  - Marine Resources Commission 1996 (Box 71)
  - Marchetti-Bonarco 1992 (Box 71)
  - MCV-M.D./PhD Program, n.d. 1989-1993 (Box 71)
  - Medicaid 1993 (Box 71)
  - Medical Assistants-Richmond Chapter, n.d. 1988, 1991 (Box 71)
  - Medical Malpractice Cap 1998-1999 (Box 71)
  - Medical Malpractice Cap (SB 1230 and HB 2469) 1999 (Box 71)
  - Mental Health and Mental Retardation 1987-1989 (Box 71)
  - Mental Health Parity (SB 430) 1999 (Box 71)
  - Midlothian Turnpike/Speed 1991 (Box 71)
  - Midlothian Village, n.d. 1988-1989 (Box 71)
  - Milan/Roach Case 1990 (Box 71)
  - Miscellaneous Legislation 1998 (Box 71)
  - Motor Vehicles 1993 (Box 71)
  - Motor Vehicles (HB 1014) 1998 (Box 71)
  - Motor Vehicles Offenses 1999 (Box 71)
  - Mrs. Hardimon, n.d. 1990-1991 (Box 71)
  - Muirfield Green 1992 (Box 71)
  - Multiple Issues 1998 (Box 71)
  - Multiple Issues 1999 (Box 71)
  - NAFTA 1992-1993 (Box 71)
  - Natural Death Act 1983, 1986 (Box 71)
  - NCSL Legisbrief 1998 (Box 71)
  - New Evidence/Capital Case Bill (HB 933) 1998 (Box 71)
  - Newborn/Hearing Tests, n.d. 1997 (Box 71)
  - News Articles 1999 (Box 71)
  - Newsletter, n.d. 1985-1994 (Box 71)
  - Newsletter 1997 (Box 71)
  - Newspaper, n.d. 1994 (Box 71)
  - Non-Constituents (HB 2324) 1999 (Box 71)
  - Nuclear Power, n.d. 1980, 1983, 1985-1990 (Box 71)
  - Nurse Midwives 1995, 1997 (Box 71)
  - Oakwood Cemetery 1997-1998 (Box 71)
  - Obesity, n.d. 1996 (Box 71)
  - Olympic Festival, n.d. 1993-1994 (Box 71)
  - Opportunity Virginia 1994 (Box 71)
  - Out of State Garbage 1998 (Box 71)
  - Outcome Based Education, n.d. (Box 71)
  - P and E-Election Law 1997 (Box 72)
  - Page Application 1991 (Box 72)
  - Page Application 1995-1997 (Box 72)
  - Pages 1998 (Box 72)
  - Parental Rights Amendment (SJ 512) 1999 (Box 72)
  - Patron Report 1986-1990 (Box 72)
  - Patron Report 1991 (Box 72)
  - Patron Report 1992 (Box 72)
  - Payroll, n.d. 1992-1995 (Box 72)
  - Pesticide Bill, n.d. 1989 (Box 72)
  - Phosphate Ban, n.d. 1986-1987 (Box 72)
  - Physician Assistants, n.d. 1998 (Box 72)
  - Piedmont Geriatric Hospital 1998 (Box 72)
  - Planned Parenthood vs. Pennsylvania 1992 (Box 72)
  - Press 1997-1998 (Box 72)
  - Prison and Parole Board, n.d. 1985-1990 (Box 72)
  - Prompt Pat Law 1984-1989 (Box 72)
  - Property Rights 1984 (Box 72)
  - Pollution Abatement 1998-1999 (Box 72)
  - Population Growth Commission, n.d. 1993-1994 (Box 72)
  - Port of Richmond Annual Report 1997 (Box 72)
  - Ports, n.d. 1986-1988 (Box 72)
  - Poultry/Environmental 1998-1999 (Box 72)
  - Poultry Waste (HB 1207) 1998, 3 folders (Box 72)
  - Powhatan Legislative Agenda 1997-1998 (Box 72)
  - Powhite, n.d. 1982-1983 (Box 72)
  - Powhite/Chesterfield County, n.d. 1982-1984 (Box 72)
  - Powhite Construction Problems, n.d. 1983-1989 (Box 72)
  - Powhite Current, n.d. 1983-1992 (Box 72)
  - Powhite/General and Campaign 1982-1984 (Box 72)
  - Powhite Parkway Extension 1983-1984 (Box 72)
  - Powhite/Sound Barriers, Right of Way 1993-1994 (Box 72)
  - Powhite Treasury Board Finance 1983 (Box 72)
  - Powhite/Virginia Department of Highways and Transportation 1983 (Box 72)
  - Practice of Healing Arts (SB 1141) 1999 (Box 72)
  - Public Private Transportation 1998 (Box 72)
  - Public Service Corp (HB 1933) 1997 (Box 72)
  - Races, n.d. 1987 (Box 72)
  - Radar Jammers (SB 7) 1997 (Box 72)
  - Radio Antennas (SB 480) 1998 (Box 72)
  - Radon 1986 (Box 72)
  - Rail-High Speed 1987 (Box 72)
  - Railroad Grade Crossings 1998 (Box 72)
  - Railroads 1985-1990 (Box 72)
  - Real Estate Appraisers License Act, n.d. 1987, 1990 (Box 73)
  - Recommendations 1998 (Box 73)
  - Recommendations 1999 (Box 73)
  - Redistricting Plans, n.d. 1982, 1989 (Box 73)
  - Redistricting Plans 1991-1997 (Box 73)
  - Referendum, n.d. 1991-1992 (Box 73)
  - Reid Scott vs. Virginia Disparity Education, n.d. 1992 (Box 73)
  - Regional Competitiveness Act 1997 (Box 73)
  - Regional Issues, n.d. 1996 (Box 73)
  - Regional Jail 1992 (Box 73)
  - Religion and Politics, n.d. 1982-1991 (Box 73)
  - Religious Freedom, n.d. 1995 (Box 73)
  - Religious Freedom (HB 1) 1998 (Box 73)
  - Religion/Public School 1995 (Box 73)
  - Report on Old Buckingham Station Fire 1995 (Box 73)
  - Request to Participate 1999 (Box 73)
  - Resume, n.d. 1997 (Box 73)
  - Retirement 1999 (Box 73)
  - Richmond Area 1997 (Box 73)
  - Richmond Center 1997 (Box 73)
  - Richmond First Club Tax and Service Report 1996 (Box 73)
  - Richmond General District Court 1998 (Box 73)
  - Richmond Legislative Program 1998 (Box 73)
  - Richmond Mayor-at-large 1995 (Box 73)
  - Richmond Metro Caucus, n.d. 1989-1992 (Box 73)
  - Right to Farm Act 1998 (Box 73)
  - Right to Farm Act 1999 (Box 73)
  - Rights-of-way Transmission Lines 1998 (Box 73)
  - Rumberg 1998 (Box 73)
  - Riverboat Gambling 1993, 1995 (Box 73)
  - Roads 1987 (Box 73)